(Amy:)Say, I heard an
interesting tidbit
(Amy:)about Howard and
Bernadette.
(Sheldon:)Really, Amy? Gossip?
(Sheldon:)I'm disappointed in you.
(Amy:)Now, now.
(Amy:)Evolutionary biologist Robin
Dunbar has identified gossip
(Amy:)as an aid to social
bonding in large groups.
(Sheldon:)Forgive my language,
but "poppycock."
(Amy:)What if he's right?
(Amy:)And by not
participating in gossip,
(Amy:)society breaks
down into
(Amy:)small feral bands of tattooed
motorcycle riders
(Amy:)fighting to the death over the
last few cans of tuna fish?
(Sheldon:)Fine.
(Sheldon:)In the parlance
of the urban music scene,
"what's the 4-1-1"?
(Amy:)Bernadette is thinking about
breaking up with Howard.
(Sheldon:)I believe our nation's
tuna cans are safe.
(Sheldon:)Excuse me.
Dr. Greene, question?
(Greene:)Yes?
(Sheldon:)You've dedicated
your life's work
(Sheldon:)to educating
the general populace
(Sheldon:)about complex scientific ideas.
(Greene:)Yes, in part.
(Sheldon:)Have you ever considered
(Sheldon:)trying to do something useful?
(Sheldon:)Perhaps, reading to the elderly?
(Greene:)Excuse me?
Yeah, but not your books;
something they might enjoy.
(Sheldon:)I kid, of course. Big fan.
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪